Louisiana Hayride Collection
Motion Picture, Broadcasting and Recorded Sound Division, Library of Congress
- Series 3. KWKH Radio and the Louisiana Hayride, 1942-2005
  - Photographs, 1942–circa 1980s, undated
    - Louisiana Hayride, primary run, 1926, 1942-1969, undated
      - Individual performers and performing groups, 1942, 1950-1969, undated
        - The Maddox Brothers & Rose performing on the Louisiana Hayride stage, circa early 1950s, McEachern, Langston, 1918-2004; 1 photographic print: black and white; 8 x 10 inches; RS 13857 P28 (Box-folder 9/4)
        - Military band assembled on stage at Barksdale Field, Louisiana, for KWKH VE Day program, [1945 May?], Army Air Forces; 1 photographic print: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P29 (Box-folder 9/4)
          Caption on front of photograph: "VE Day program transcription, Barksdale Field, LA."
        - Snapshot of Frankie Miller, Shelby Singleton, Margie Singleton, Dee Mullins, and Merle Kilgore, backstage at the Louisiana Hayride, 1959 November, 1 photographic print: black and white; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 inches; RS 13857 P30 (Box-folder 9/5)
        - Dolly Parton publicity photograph, circa 1967, 1 photographic print: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P31 (Box-folder 9/5)
        - Minnie Pearl performing on stage at the Louisiana Hayride, 1950s, 2 photographic prints: black and white; 5 x 7 inches and 10 1/2 x 8 1/4 inches; RS 13857 P32; RS 13857 P33 (Box-folder 9/5)
        - Webb Pierce and unidentified woman holding Southern Maid donuts, 1949-1952, 1 photographic print: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P34 (Box-folder 9/5)
          see also Norm Bale, Webb Pierce, and Jeff Dale, 1950s
        - Johnny Seay publicity photographs, circa 1958-1961, 3 photographic prints: black and white; 11 x 8 1/2 inches; RS 13857 P35–RS 13857 P37 (Box-folder 9/5)
        - Nat Stuckey performing on stage at the Louisiana Hayride, 1960, 1 photographic print: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P38 (Box-folder 9/6)
        - Ernest Tubb publicity photograph, circa 1950s, 1 photographic print: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P39 (Box-folder 9/6)
          Autographed, with handwritten message on front: "Good luck to everyone connected with the Hayride."
        - Slim Whitman, circa early 1950s
          - Slim Whitman and Mrs. [Horace?] Logan snapshot, circa early 1950s, 1 photographic print: black and white; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 inches; RS 13857 P40 (Box-folder 9/6)
            Handwritten on back of photograph: "Mrs. Logan, Slim Whitman."
          - Slim Whitman performing for KWKH, 1953, McEachern, Langston, 1918-2004; 1 photographic print: black and white; 8 x 10 inches; RS 13857 P41 (Box-folder 9/6)
        - Hank Williams photographs, 1952, undated
          see also Tommy Hill, Hank Williams, "Socko" Sokolowski, and Johnny Horton, 1949-1953
          - Publicity photograph of Hank Williams on stage at the Louisiana Hayride, 1952 November, Patterson, A. C.; 1 photographic print: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P42 (Box-folder 9/6)
          - Hank Williams snapshot with [Ray Carlisle?], between 1949 and 1953, 1 photographic print: black and white; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 inches; RS 13857 P43 (Box-folder 9/6)
          - Portrait photograph of Hank Williams, circa 1949, McEachern, Langston, 1918-2004; 1 photographic print: black and white; 7 x 5 inches; RS 13857 P44 (Box-folder 9/6)
        - Photographs of unidentified performers, undated, 3 photographic prints: black and white; 11 x 8 1/2 inches; RS 13857 P45–RS 13857 RS 47 (Box-folder 9/7)
          One of the photographs is credited to Langston McEachern.
      - Hosts and announcers, circa late 1940s–1950s, undated
        - Norm Bale photographs, 1950s
          Most of the photographs show Norm Bale with Louisiana Hayride performers.
          see also Louisiana Governor Jimmie Davis sits at a piano while Norm Bale, [Horace Logan?], and a group of musicians look on, at Davis's home, 1953 and Frank Page with Louisiana Hayride performers and hosts, [between 1948 and 1958?]
          - Norm Bale displays a box of Southern Maid donuts, circa 1950s, Graham's Studio, Shreveport, Louisiana; 1 photographic print: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P48 (Box-folder 9/8)
          - Norm Bale with child, late 1940s–early 1950s, Eschenfelder, Cliff; 1 photographic print: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P49 (Box-folder 9/8)
            The child appears to have drawn a sweepstakes ticket from a revolving drum to which a Holsum bread advertisement is attached.
          - Norm Bale, Ferlin Husky, and Tillman Franks posing informally, circa 1950s, Graham's Studio, Shreveport, Louisiana; 1 photographic print: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P50 (Box-folder 9/8)
          - Norm Bale, Webb Pierce, and Jeff Dale, 1950s, Graham's Studio, Shreveport, Louisiana; 1 photographic print: black and white; 8 x 10 inches; RS 13857 P51 (Box-folder 9/8)
            For an additional photograph of Webb Pierce, see also Webb Pierce and unidentified woman holding Southern Maid donuts, 1949-1952
          - Snapshot of Tex Ritter, Norm Bale, and unidentified man, circa 1950s, 1 photographic print: black and white; 3 1/4 x 4 1/4 inches; RS 13857 P52 (Box-folder 9/8)
          - Snapshot of Norm Bale posing with three unidentified young women [performers?], circa 1950s, 1 photographic print: black and white; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 inches; RS 13857 P53 (Box-folder 9/8)
        - Jeff Dale Louisiana Hayride publicity photograph, circa 1948-1958, 1 photographic print: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P54 (Box-folder 9/9)
          Dale was a Louisiana Hayride announcer during the period 1948-1958.
          see also Frank Page with Louisiana Hayride performers and hosts, [between 1948 and 1958?]
          Handwritten message on front of photograph: "To Evelyn: In this business I meet a host of people. Some I remember, some I forget. I remember those because of good things others have said about them. You are one that I remember. In friendship, Jeff."
        - Horace "Hoss" Logan publicity photographs and snapshot, 1953, undated, 3 photographic prints: black and white; 8 1/2 x 11 inches, 10 x 8 inches, and 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 inches; RS 13857 P55–RS 13857 P57 (Box-folder 9/9)
        - Frank Page with Louisiana Hayride performers and hosts, [between 1948 and 1958?]
          For additional photographs of Frank Page, see also Johnny Horton and Frank Page snapshot, circa 1954-1960, Concert to celebrate the 50th anniversary of Elvis Presley's first appearance on the Louisiana Hayride, at the Municipal Auditorium, Shreveport, 2004 October 16, and Frank Page and Tillman Franks at a celebration honoring Elvis Presley's 71st birthday, at the Municipal Auditorium, Shreveport, 2006 January 8. For additional photographs of Norm Bale, see also Norm Bale photographs, 1950s. For additional photographs of Jeff Dale, see also Jeff Dale Louisiana Hayride publicity photograph, circa 1948-1958
          - Frank Page speaks with Eddie Albert while Jeff Dale and Norm Bale look on, between 1948 and 1958, Graham's Studio, Shreveport, Louisiana; 1 photographic print: black and white; 8 x 10 inches; RS 13857 P58 (Box-folder 9/10)
          - Frank Page, Norm Bale, and Horace Logan group portrait photograph, [between 1948 and 1958?], 1 photographic print: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P59 (Box-folder 9/10)
          - Frank Page, Jeff Dale, and Norm Bale with unidentified groups on Louisiana Hayride stage, [between 1948 and 1958?], 1 photographic print: black and white; 8 x 10 inches; RS 13857 P60 (Box-folder 9/10)
          - Frank Page and Norm Bale with unidentified group on Louisiana Hayride stage, [between 1948 and 1958?], 1 photographic print: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P61 (Box-folder 9/10)
      - Miscellaneous people and events, circa late 1940s, 1963, and undated, 5 photographic prints: black and white; 8 x 10 inches, 10 x 8 inches, and 6 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P62–RS 13857 P66; 3 of the photographs are unidentified portrait and group photos. (Box-folder 9/11)
        - Louisiana Department of Agriculture representatives and others showcasing Lapesco brand fancy shelled pecans, with KWKH banner in the background, at the Louisiana State Fair, 1963, 1 photographic print: black and white; 8 x 10 inches; RS 13857 P62 (Box-folder 9/11)
        - Miss Haynesville and Miss Bossier City parade past the Shreveport Municipal Auditorium in convertibles, circa late 1940s, 1 photographic print: black and white; 8 x 10 inches; RS 13857 P63 (Box-folder 9/11)
    - Louisiana Hayride, secondary run, circa 1970s–1980s
      Photographs are predominantly promotional images of performers from the Louisiana Hayride's secondary run, which was produced by Shreveport businessman David Kent from 1974 to 1987. Also shown are people and places associated with this period of Louisiana Hayride history. In its first year, the program was known as Hayride U.S.A., but in 1975 the title reverted to Louisiana Hayride.
      - Individual performers and performing groups, circa 1970s–1980s
        - A.T. & Georgia publicity photograph, circa 1970s, 1 photographic print: black and white; 8 x 10 inches; RS 13857 P67 (Box-folder 9/12)
          Autographed: "Mr. Dave, Thanks for a shot. Love, A.T. & Georgia."
        - Jim Ed Brown publicity photograph, circa 1974, 1 photographic print: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P68 (Box-folder 9/12)
          Autographed: "To Hayride - U.S.A.! Thanks for all the help & my best to you. Looking forward to our 1st visit. Sincerely, Jim Ed Brown."
        - Catfish South, 1975 May 17, 3 photographic prints: color; 4 x 5 and 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 inches; RS 13857 P69–RS 13857 P71 (Box-folder 9/12)
          Catfish South was the Louisiana Hayride house band during the program's secondary run. It consisted of Jerry Tanner on rhythm guitar, Larry Page on drums, Noel Odom on lead guitar, Bobby Kelly on bass, Ron Riley on steel, and Ron Di Iulio on piano.
          Handwritten on the back of the two larger photographs: "Catfish. May 17, 1975, Hayride U.S.A.!"
        - Jerry Clower publicity photograph, circa 1970, 1 photographic print: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P72 (Box-folder 9/12)
          Autographed on front: "God bless you. Jerry Clower."
        - Craig Dillingham, circa 1970s, 1 photographic print: black and white; 5 x 3 1/2 inches; 1 contact print: black and white; 2 x 1 1/2 inches; RS 13857 P73-RS 13857 P74 (Box-folder 9/12)
        - Micki Fuhrman photographs, circa mid 1970s–1980s
          Included are publicity photographs, images of Fuhrman performing on stage with one or more backup musicians or with other vocalists, and group photos with musicians and Louisiana Hayride owners and staff.
          see also Group portrait photographs taken at ATV Music Group headquarters, Nashville, Tennessee, circa 1981, and Micki Fuhrman negatives, circa late 1970s–early 1980s
          - Micki Fuhrman publicity and performance photographs, circa mid 1970s–1980s, 8 photographic prints: black and white; 8 x 10 inches or smaller; RS 13857 P75–RS 13857 P82 (Box-folder 9/13)
          - Group portraits with Micki Furhman, circa mid 1970s–1980s, 4 photographic prints: black and white; 8 x 10 inches and 5 x 7 inches; RS 13857 P83–RS 13857 P86 (Box-folder 9/14)
          - Micki Fuhrman with David Kent and others, circa mid 1970s–early 1980s, 6 photographic prints: black and white; 8 x 10 inches or smaller; 1 photographic print: color; 5 x 3 1/2 inches; RS 13857 P87–RS 13857 P93 (Box-folder 9/15)
            Images show Micki Fuhrman and David Kent with other unidentified individuals, possibly including other members of the Nashville Sound Trio.
            For additional photographs of David Kent, see also Photographs of David Kent and associated songwriters, music industry figures, and locations, circa 1970s–1980s
          - Micki Fuhrman contact sheets, circa mid 1970s, 2 contact sheets, 6 partial contact sheets: black and white; 35 mm and 2 1/2 x 2 1/4 inches (Box-folder 9/16)
            Includes individual and group images of Micki Fuhrman in performance and posing for portrait photographs.
            One of the contact sheets, and one of the partial contact sheets (a strip of six frames cut from a contact sheet) also include images of Noel Odom playing guitar.
        - Bill Pickett portrait photograph, circa mid 1970s–mid 1980s, 1 photographic print: black and white; 4 1/2 x 3 1/2 inches; RS 13857 P94 (Box-folder 9/17)
        - Jeanne Pruett publicity photograph, circa mid 1970s, 1 photographic print: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P95 (Box-folder 9/17)
          Autographed on front: "To Hayride U.S.A. Enjoyed much. Jeanne Pruett."
        - Bobby G. Rice publicity photograph, circa 1973, 1 photographic print: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P96 (Box-folder 9/17)
          Autographed: "[Carla?], Great meeting you. Bobby G. Rice."
        - David Rogers publicity photograph, circa mid 1970s, 1 photographic print: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P97 (Box-folder 9/17)
          Autographed: "To Hayride U.S.A., Love ya, David Rogers."
        - Eddy Sims publicity photograph, circa mid 1970s–1980s, 1 photographic print: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P98 (Box-folder 9/17)
          Autographed: "Yours truly, Eddy Sims."
        - The Stonemasons, publicity photograph, circa 1970s, 1 photographic print: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P99 (Box-folder 9/17)
          Autographed: "Love ya! The Stonemasons."
        - Smokey Stover publicity photograph, circa 1970s–1980s, 1 photographic print: color; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P100 (Box-folder 9/17)
        - Shoji Tabuchi Louisiana Hayride photographs, circa mid 1970s–1980s, 7 photographic prints: black and white; 5 x 3 1/2 inches; RS 13857 P101–RS 13857 P107 (Box-folder 9/18)
        - Porter Wagoner publicity photograph, circa 1967–mid 1970s, 1 photographic print: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P108 (Box-folder 9/19)
          Autographed: "Best of luck to Hayride U.S.A. Porter."
        - Freddy Weller publicity photograph, circa mid 1970s, 1 photographic print: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P109 (Box-folder 9/19)
          Autographed: "To Hayride U.S.A. Many thanks--Freddy Weller."
        - Justin Wilson portrait photograph, circa mid 1970s–mid 1980s, 1 photographic print: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P110 (Box-folder 9/19)
          Autographed: "A mon ami, David. Justin Wilson."
        - Karen Wiltz, 1975 May 17, undated, 3 photographic prints: black and white; 5 x 4 inches, 7 1/8 x 7 1/8 inches, and 10 x 8 inches; 2 photographic prints: color; 5 x 4 inches; 1 contact sheet: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P111–RS 13857 P115 (Box-folder 9/20)
        - Unidentified performers, circa 1970s–early 1980s, 1 photographic print: black and white; 7 x 5 inches; 2 photographic prints: color; 3 1/2 x 4 1/2 inches and 4 x 6 inches; 6 partial contact sheets: black and white; 9 1/4 x 1 1/2 inches or smaller; RS 13857 P116–RS 13857 P118 (Box-folder 9/21)
          Photographs show mostly performers who presumably were associated with the Hayride U.S.A./Louisiana Hayride program.
          Contact sheets were cut into strips and individual contact prints. These items do not currently have item IDs.
      - David Kent and associated songwriters, music industry figures, and locations, circa 1970s-1980s
        see also Micki Fuhrman with David Kent and others, circa mid 1970s-early 1980s
        - David Kent photographs, circa 1970s-1980s, 9 photographic prints: black and white; 8 x 10 inches or smaller; 3 photographic prints: color; 3 1/2 x 4 1/2 inches and 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 inches; RS 13857 P119–RS 13857 P129 (Box-folder 9/22)
          Primarily portrait photographs of Hayride president and owner David Kent (secondary run, 1974-1987). Also included are images of Kent with program musicians and staff, speaking at a Louisiana Hayride podium, and speaking into a radio microphone.
          Two of the approximately 5 x 4-inch black and white prints are duplicates.
        - Group portrait photographs taken at ATV Music Group headquarters, Nashville, Tennessee, circa 1981
          For additional images of Micki Fuhrman, see also Micki Fuhrman photographs, circa mid 1970s–1980s and Micki Fuhrman negatives, circa late 1970s–early 1980s
          - ATV Music Group staff in front of the offices at 1217 16th Avenue, Nashville, circa 1981, 2 photographic prints black and white; 8 x 10 inches and 5 x 7 inches; RS 13857 P130; RS 13857 P131 (Box-folder 9/23)
            From left to right: Dennis Knutson, Margaret Jones, Gerry Teifer, Jay Remington Wilde, Byron Hill, Jean Williams, Jim Rushing, Rick Schulman, Eddie Burton, and Micki Fuhrman.
          - Micki Fuhrman, David Kent, and Gerry Teifer group portrait photograph, ATV Music Group offices, Nashville, circa 1981, 2 photographic prints: black and white; 8 x 10 inches; RS 13857 P132; RS 13857 P132 (copy 2) (Box-folder 9/23)
          - Gerry Teifer, Byron Hill, Jim Rushing, and Micki Fuhrman group portrait photograph, ATV Music Group offices, Nashville, circa 1981, 1 photographic print: black and white; 5 x 7 inches; RS 13857 P133 (Box-folder 9/23)
          - Micki Fuhrman, David Kent, and Gerry Teifer group portrait photograph, ATV Music Group offices, Nashville, circa 1981, 3 photographic prints: black and white; 5 x 7 inches, 3 1/2 x 5 inches, and 5 x 3 1/2 inches; RS 13857 P134–RS 13857 P136 (Box-folder 9/23)
            Two of the photographs are nearly exact duplicates (in different sizes), while the third copy shows only Kent and Teifer.
        - Various places associated with the Louisiana Hayride's secondary run, circa 1976, undated
          - Images of Louisiana Hayride venues, circa 1976 April and undated, 5 photographic prints: black and white; 5 x 5 inches and approximately 5 x 3 1/2 inches; RS 13857 P137–RS 13857 P140 (copy 2) (Box-folder 9/24)
            Photographic prints show the Louisiana Hayride auditorium in Bossier City, Louisiana, with sign in front that reads: "The Louisiana Hayride, home of the Hayride Kitchen." Also shown are billboards at a Holiday Inn and at the Brownwood Coliseum, Brownwood, Texas, welcoming the Louisiana Hayride.
          - Sound Lab Recording Studio, Nashville, Tennessee, circa 1976 April
            Exterior and interior views of the Sound Lab recording studio in Nashville, Tennessee.
            Negatives and corresponding contact sheet.
            - Safety film negatives, 19 safety film negatives (4 strips) black and white; 35 mm (Box-folder OSU 1/1-4)
              For additional images in this format, see also Safety film negatives, circa late 1970s-early 1980s
            - Contact sheet, 1 contact sheet: black and white; 8 x 10 inches (Box-folder 9/24)
  - Photographic reproductions and illustrations, circa 1940s–1980s, 18 prints: 1 color; 8 1/2 x 11 inches and smaller (Box-folder 9/25)
    Includes images of musicians who performed at the Louisiana Hayride over the years. Some of the illustrations accompany descriptive text, song lyrics, or sheet music, and many have been autographed.
    Musicians shown include Buddy Attaway and Claude King, 1952 (autographed); the Bailes Brothers (Johnnie and Walter) (autographed); Cousin Wilbur and Blondie Brooks, 1949 (autographed); Sonny Harville, Bob Murphy, Tex Grimsley, Don Davis, and Ray Belcher performing at the Louisiana Hayride, April 3, 1948; the Ray Hendrix Show (autographed); Johnny Horton (4 prints); Frankie Miller (autographed); Webb Pierce (autographed), with Jack Greene on reverse side; Ernest Tubb (autographed), with Conway Twitty on reverse side (autographed); Paul Warren, Clyde Baum, Ray Atkins, Jack Anglin, and Johnnie Wright, with Frank Page and Ray Bartlett; Curley Williams and his Georgia Peach Pickers; Hank Williams; the York Brothers (Leslie and George) (autographed); and an unidentified band (with the music to "Little Paper Boy" on reverse side) [Johnny & Jack and the Tennessee Mountain Boys with Kitty Wells? circa 1949?].
  - Safety film negatives, circa late 1970s-early 1980s
    For additional images in this format, see also Sound Lab Recording Studio, safety film negatives
    - Micki Fuhrman negatives, circa late 1970s–early 1980s
      For photographic prints of Mick Fuhrman, see also Micki Fuhrman photographs, circa mid 1970s-1980s and the Group portrait photographs taken at ATV Music Group headquarters, Nashville, Tennessee, circa 1981
      - Micki Fuhrman at the Grand Ole Opry, circa early 1980s, 65 safety film negatives (on 15 strips): black and white; 35 mm (Box-folder OSU 1/5-19)
        Negatives show Micki Fuhrman alone; singing; speaking and standing with [David Kent?] and other individuals; and standing on stage [at the Ryman Auditorium?].
        Handwritten on original negative sleeve: "Micki at the Opry."
      - Micki Fuhrman portrait photographs, circa early 1980s, 21 safety film negatives (on 6 strips): black and white; 4 x 6 cm (Box-folder OSU 1/20-25)
        Negatives show Micki Fuhrman alone and with [David Kent?] in what appears to be an office setting.
    - Unidentified performers, undated, 6 safety film negatives (on 1 strip): black and white; 35 mm (Box-folder OSU 1/26)
      Two unidentified male instrumentalists perform at the Louisiana Hayride.
- Series 4. Elvis Presley and the Louisiana Hayride, 1956-1994
  Series 4 includes ephemera, photographs, and newspaper articles regarding Elvis Presley's performances at the Louisiana Hayride.
  - Ephemera, 1994
    - KWKH's Louisiana Hayride: souvenir album (Box-folder 3/3)
      Reproduction of an original Louisiana Hayride souvenir program from March 1956 featuring Elvis Presley as a performer. The program was probably reproduced in 1994 in honor of the 40th anniversary of Presley's initial performance at the Louisiana Hayride.
    - Elvis at the Louisiana Hayride, 40th anniversary: October 16, 1954 – October 16, 1994, 1994 (Box-folder 3/4)
      Program for a commemorative concert.
  - Newspaper articles, 1956-1987, undated (Box-folder 3/5)
    Includes a photocopied article from The Shreveport Times describing Elvis Presley's departure from the Louisiana Hayride, various original and reproduced retrospective articles highlighting Presley's ties to the Louisiana Hayride, and articles in honor of Presley after his death in 1977.
  - Photographic prints, circa 1954-2006 January
    - Elvis Presley portrait photographs, circa 1954-1956, 2 photographic prints: black and white; 7 x 5 inches and 8 x 10 inches; RS 13857 P141–RS 13857 P142 (Box-folder 9/26)
    - Elvis Presley and his band performing on stage at the Louisiana Hayride
      For additional photographs of D.J. Fontana, see also Concert to celebrate the 50th anniversary of Elvis Presley's first appearance on the Louisiana Hayride, at the Municipal Auditorium, Shreveport, 2004 October 16. For additional photographs of Scotty Moore, see also Scotty Moore performing on stage, circa late 1990s or early 2000s
      - Elvis Presley performing with Scotty Moore and Bill Black, circa 1954-1955, 1 photographic print: black and white; 5 x 3 1/2 inches; RS 13857 P143 (Box-folder 9/27)
      - Elvis Presley performing with Scotty Moore, D.J. Fontana, and Bill Black, 1955 January 2, 1 photographic print: black and white; 5 x 3 3/4 inches; RS 13857 P144 (Box-folder 9/27)
      - Elvis Presley on stage with Scotty Moore, D.J. Fontana, and Bill Black in their final Louisiana Hayride performance, at the Hirsch Youth Building, Louisiana State Fairgrounds, Shreveport, 1956 December 15
        - Elvis Presley on stage with Scotty Moore, D.J. Fontana, and Bill Black, 1956 December 15, Kinel, Ben; 1 photographic print: black and white; 10 x 8 inches; RS 13857 P145 (Box-folder 9/27)